Unlike a while ago, I'm wearing a skirt today.
ちょっと前と違って、今日はスカートなんだね
My legs are long...
足長いなぁ...
Even though I'm short
身長低いのに
...
I didn't wrap it the other day.
この 前くるませなかったね
We're good friends...
仲だし...
You said you'd let me.
させてくれるって言ってたじゃん
Is it okay?
いいの?
Really.
本当に
You can take back the one you just had.
今のが引き返せますよ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
thank you very much.
どうもありがとうございました
Unlike a while ago, I'm wearing a skirt today.
ちょっと前と違って、今日はスカートなんだね
My legs are long...
足長いなぁ...
Even though I'm short
身長低いのに
...
I didn't wrap it the other day.
この 前くるませなかったね
We're good friends...
仲だし...
You said you'd let me.
させてくれるって言ってたじゃん
Is it okay?
いいの?
Really.
本当に
You can take back the one you just had.
今のが引き返せますよ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
TRUE?
本当?
why?
なんで?
Did you give me OK?
OKしてくれた?
feeling?
気分?
That's right.
そうだよね
Everyone is right.
皆さん はそうですよ
I can't climb my throat without momentum.
今 のどりはね、勢いがないとできないの
Are you nervous?
緊張してるの?
still.
まだ
Well then, let's relieve some tension.
じゃあちょっと緊張をほぐそうか
There...
そこでね...
Try raising your legs a little
ちょっと足を上げてみて
hey.
ね
Try adding one more.
もう 一つも上げてみて
Is that like bisepang?
それ、ビセパンみたいなのかな?
We're connected.
繋がってるんだ
That's naughty.
やらしいね
what happened?
どうしたの?
There.
そこでね
Look this way.
こっち向いてね
It's a skirt.
スカートね
What is this?
これなんだ?
It drops a lot.
すっごい落とすね
It came so fast
すっごいピチョピチョやってきた
hey.
ね
Why are you licking me?
なん で舐めんの?
While people piled up.
人が積もりながら
Can you put it in at a glance?
一目で入れれるかな?
Can I put it in this position?
この体勢で入れれるかな?
You're so wet.
すっごい濡れてるね
You can remember what you like.
好 きなの覚えていいんだよ
I can't move.
動けへん
Can't move?
動けない?
So, did it move?
じゃあ動いたっけよっか
You're going to sleep.
寝るんだね
We have practice today, so move lightly.
今日練習だから、軽く動いてこな
Slowly.
ゆっくりと
Ah, it feels good.
あ、気持ちいい
You can do it.
できるね
difficult?
難しい?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
It's good because I can sleep peacefully on my own.
自分でゆっくりパンパン寝れるからいいぞ
It feels good.
気持ちいいぞ
Oh, oh, I fell.
あ、あ、落ちちゃったよ
This thing fell off.
落 ちちゃったよ、これ
It suits me so well.
すっごい合ってるよ
Check out the lunch from here.
こっちからランチ見てください
That's terrible.
やばいね
lunch.
ランチ
like?
好き?
Yeah, I like it.
うん、好き
Because it was a cold place.
寒い場所があったから
That's fine, uncle.
いいでしょ、おじさんの
I'll go.
行くよ
Go, go, go.
行く行く
The small one went all the way in.
ちっちゃいのが奥まで入っちゃったね
Let's cut it out and write it out.
切って書き出してあげよう
It will be difficult if you try to be patient.
忍心したら大変だからね
If you have patience, it will be difficult, so let's get it out.
忍心したら大変だから出しておこう
Because it's difficult.
大変だからね
Shinobu: If you feel like it, let's put it out properly.
忍 心したらちゃんと出しておこう
Uncle, I'll give you a hand.
おじさん手も出してあげるから
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってよ
Because it's dangerous.
危ないからね
It's going to be tough, so I really need to let it out.
大変だからね、出しておかないと本当に
I came out because it would be difficult if I tried to be ninja.
忍心したら大変だから出たよ
It came out fine.
ちゃんと出てきたよ
Uncle's player selection is over.
おじさんの選手選命も終わりだよ
Look up a little.
ちょっと向き上がってみて
I'd like to hear about the possibility.
可能性聞きたいんだけどね
Lastly, do you just want to ask for a foul?
最後に反則だけお願いしたいんですか?
What made it so hard?
こんだけハードにしたことは
copper?
どう?